<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CommerceV3</title>
    <link>http://www.commercev3.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CommerceV3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 16:11:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.commercev3.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Build New Revenue with Remarketing for Search</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/05/2016-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/05/2016-05-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Remarketing lists for search ads (RLSAs) are a great way to enhance your current Adwords campaigns. They also let you bid on highly competitive keywords that might otherwise be too expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend you use RLSAs to capture revenue from site abandoners. When visitors leave your website without making a purchase, use these ads to reconnect with them as they continue searching Google. You can set your bids or select keywords more aggressively since these visitors have recently visited your website and/or shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two basic strategies we recommend for search ads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize bids&lt;/em&gt; for your existing keywords or ad groups for those visitors on your remarketing lists. We typically increase our bids at least 100% and in some cases up to 300% when marketing to existing website visitors. This is a great way to be aggressive in the competitive Google Shopping area as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.commercev3.com/blogimages/remarketing-article-screenshot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Build New Revenue with Remarketing for Search | CommerceV3.com&#34; title=&#34;Remarketing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize Keywords:&lt;/em&gt; You can bid on keywords that you wouldn’t normally include when you’re focused on just shoppers who have recently visited your site. For example, bid on generic keywords only for people who have visited your site in the last 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reminder: Unlike Display Remarketing, which only requires 100 cookies before the list can be used, a remarketing list for Google search ads needs to have a minimum number of 1,000 cookies before the list can be used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in seeing what Remarketing for Search can do for your sales? Or looking for a broader digital marketing strategy checkup? The CV3 Marketing team can help. &lt;a href=&#34;marketing@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test2</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/events/test2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/events/test2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Remarketing lists for search ads (RLSAs) are a great way to enhance your current Adwords campaigns. They also let you bid on highly competitive keywords that might otherwise be too expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend you use RLSAs to capture revenue from site abandoners. When visitors leave your website without making a purchase, use these ads to reconnect with them as they continue searching Google. You can set your bids or select keywords more aggressively since these visitors have recently visited your website and/or shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two basic strategies we recommend for search ads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize bids&lt;/em&gt; for your existing keywords or ad groups for those visitors on your remarketing lists. We typically increase our bids at least 100% and in some cases up to 300% when marketing to existing website visitors. This is a great way to be aggressive in the competitive Google Shopping area as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.commercev3.com/blogimages/remarketing-article-screenshot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Build New Revenue with Remarketing for Search | CommerceV3.com&#34; title=&#34;Remarketing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize Keywords:&lt;/em&gt; You can bid on keywords that you wouldn’t normally include when you’re focused on just shoppers who have recently visited your site. For example, bid on generic keywords only for people who have visited your site in the last 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reminder: Unlike Display Remarketing, which only requires 100 cookies before the list can be used, a remarketing list for Google search ads needs to have a minimum number of 1,000 cookies before the list can be used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in seeing what Remarketing for Search can do for your sales? Or looking for a broader digital marketing strategy checkup? The CV3 Marketing team can help. &lt;a href=&#34;marketing@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CommCon 2016:  The 2016 Communiqué User Conference</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/events/commcon-2016-the-2016-communique-user-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/events/commcon-2016-the-2016-communique-user-conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2016 Communiqué User Conference is a solutions oriented conference with great content, tons of networking with other Communiqué and Stone Edge users, and lots of practical ideas in an intimate setting at the Walt Disney World Swan and Dolphin Resort.  We are certain you will agree this is the can’t-miss conference of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Register today to reserve your seat for the 2nd annual Communiqué User Conference - CommCon 2016. Attendance is limited to the first 150 attendees, so sign up now to &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.altaireon.com/commcon_2016/commcon_registration_2016.html&#34;&gt;reserve your seat&lt;/a&gt; before it’s sold out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event is scheduled for April 1st - 3rd, 2016&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is this?</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/05/2016-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/05/2016-05-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Remarketing lists for search ads (RLSAs) are a great way to enhance your current Adwords campaigns. They also let you bid on highly competitive keywords that might otherwise be too expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend you use RLSAs to capture revenue from site abandoners. When visitors leave your website without making a purchase, use these ads to reconnect with them as they continue searching Google. You can set your bids or select keywords more aggressively since these visitors have recently visited your website and/or shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two basic strategies we recommend for search ads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize bids&lt;/em&gt; for your existing keywords or ad groups for those visitors on your remarketing lists. We typically increase our bids at least 100% and in some cases up to 300% when marketing to existing website visitors. This is a great way to be aggressive in the competitive Google Shopping area as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.commercev3.com/blogimages/remarketing-article-screenshot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Build New Revenue with Remarketing for Search | CommerceV3.com&#34; title=&#34;Remarketing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Optimize Keywords:&lt;/em&gt; You can bid on keywords that you wouldn’t normally include when you’re focused on just shoppers who have recently visited your site. For example, bid on generic keywords only for people who have visited your site in the last 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reminder: Unlike Display Remarketing, which only requires 100 cookies before the list can be used, a remarketing list for Google search ads needs to have a minimum number of 1,000 cookies before the list can be used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in seeing what Remarketing for Search can do for your sales? Or looking for a broader digital marketing strategy checkup? The CV3 Marketing team can help. &lt;a href=&#34;marketing@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Success Story: Kitchen Kettle Village</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/04/2016-04-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/2016/04/2016-04-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Next up in our client success series, we’d like to introduce you to Kitchen Kettle Village (shop.kitchenkettle.com), and its Operations Coach, Chris Dydol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nestled in Lancaster County’s Pennsylvania Dutch Country, Kitchen Kettle has a sweetly charming entrepreneur’s story behind it: Founder Pat Burnley and her husband, Bob, started their business in their garage, preserving jams and jellies. Soon, the garage itself became a tourist attraction, as visitors stopped by to observe the jelly-making process, and enjoy a cup of coffee and a sample of freshly made jellies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, that garage start-up has grown into an expansive shopping destination, with more than 40 retail tenants, including clothing shops, food crafters, artisans, restaurants, and visitor lodging, plus regular food festivals and special events to foster a community experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.commercev3.com/blogimages/kkv-homepage-screenshot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KitchenKettle.com Home Page&#34; title=&#34;Kitchen Kettle&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris shares with us Kitchen Kettle’s eCommerce experience and history with CV3:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3: How are you selling products today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KKV:  The main outlet is a physical shop within our Village of 40 retail shops. We also wholesale products, and obviously sell online via CV3.
What caused you to seek a solution like CommerceV3?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially we were looking for customization of product purchasing method, and being able to have a site that could represent not only our brick and mortar shopping experience, but also our entire Village shopping experience.
CV3: Did your company already have a solution in place? Is there a specific incident that stands out that made it obvious a new solution was needed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We originally had been with CV3, and then considered alternative online shopping vendors upon the suggestion of an external marketing agency.  We quickly realized that other vendors’ platforms were not able to handle our custom requests in a cost efficient manner.
As you searched for a solution, what questions were you looking to have answered?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customization – to fit our current shopping experience but also to have the ability to grow as our Village grows.  We were also very concerned with the level of direct support available as we grow.
How long have you been using CommerceV3 at your company at this point?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started in 2011, and then begin our “version 2.0” for about 1 month now.
How are you using CommerceV3 in your everyday operations?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our online store presence feeds directly into our own internal order processing/fulfillment system.
What features/capabilities do you use the most? Are you leveraging our solution for any interesting/unexpected use cases?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quantity discounting, recipe suggestions, related product suggestions, and promo code capability.
What overall business benefits have you seen since implementing our solution?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average order has increased, along with the benefit of having the online shopping experience that resembles the shopping experience in our Village.
What process improvements have you seen, such as fewer mistakes, better data management, reduced time/costs, etc.?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve noted less guest confusion in regards to product selection, especially from different size categories.
What improvements have you seen in your services to your own customers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flexibility in ordering, improved ease of shopping our various product lines.
What are the company goals that you hope to accomplish in the future that you can share?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continued sustainable online sales growth by adding additional “stores” within the site to emulate and enhance our guest’s shopping experience, and expand our online product lines in conjunction with our Village concept.
A big thank you to Kitchen Kettle Village and Chris Dydol for sharing their experiences with us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to share your company’s story, let us know!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/about-us/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;When you have a problem, you will get a knowledgeable person on the phone who will fix your issues the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the platform, the entire company is web-based, meaning everyone works from a space of their own choosing. It’s good for the environment and it helps us get more done, faster!  We are a company of innovators and technology rockstars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;leadership-team&#34;&gt;Leadership Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;blake-ellis&#34;&gt;Blake Ellis&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Founding Partner &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blake Ellis often gets tagged as a “serial entrepreneur”, having been involved in a number of web-based start-ups. Most of his efforts fail spectacularly, but the ones that survive seem to do very well. In addition to CommerceV3, the successes include Rails Machine, Smack Dab Studios, ResEngine, and Timberline Interactive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blake has won numerous technology awards for CommerceV3 and Rails Machine, including the CBETA Innovation Award and graduation from the Advanced Technology Development Center at Georgia Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;nathan-focht&#34;&gt;Nathan Focht&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Founding Partner &amp;amp; President&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathan is the heart and soul of CommerceV3, relentlessly driving the platform from its humble beginnings to ever greater heights. He is quick to answer his cell phone, even when things are going wrong, and he’s just as quick to give you a straight and honest answer, even if you were wanting a bit of fluff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More catalog merchant than software developer, Nathan breaks new ground by reinventing tried and true retail techniques to sell more online. He re-envisioned “square inch analysis,” a staple of print catalogs, and brought it into the 21st century for application to online sales. He routinely devises new ways of offering customer segmentation and promo codes, something you will love and hate if you ever have the opportunity to sift through the thousands of permutations available in CV3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathan has won numerous awards for CommerceV3 and was the driving force behind the 2009 acquisition of Timberline Interactive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV3 Templates Quick Start</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/docs/cv3-templates-quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/docs/cv3-templates-quick-start/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creating a new store in CV3 is easy. Just click “Create Store” in the left nav, give your store a name and leave the default choices in place (two-column layout, include sample data). Click the “Add Store” button at the bottom of the form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You have a fully functional e-commerce storefront. Just click on your new store’s name to visit it’s dashboard, then click the “Staging” link just to the right of the CV3 logo at the top of the page. A new window (or tab) will open up and you can shop in your store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve got everything: site search, category listings, newsletter sign-up, product pages, shopping cart… even a member section. There’s just one problem. It doesn’t match your brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, it’s a bit gray and down right ugly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default templates may not be much to look at, but they’re the perfect foundation for learning about CV3. They include more sample code than you’ll ever need to look at, because it’s rare that a store implements all the features in the default template set. In fact, you may start deleting more things than you add, but that’s okay… deleting is easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let’s start getting our hands dirty and get this store ready for customers.
&lt;h3&gt;STYLING WITH CSS&lt;/h3&gt;
Editing your Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) is the fastest way to start styling your store. If you’re not familiar with CSS, you can Google for tutorials or check out the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.csszengarden.com/&#34;&gt;CSS Zen Garden&lt;/a&gt; to see how just working with style sheets can radically change the look of a site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 offers direct access to all the styles that make up your store. Open up the Design section in the left navigation (click on the blue “pillbox” named Design), then click on Template Library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The templates in your library are grouped together by type, and the first group is called CSS Stylesheets. Click on this name or the plus sign to open up the group, then click on styles.css or the edit button to the right of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s your CSS! You can make any changes you want, or you can copy/paste additional styles from external editors. You can click the Save button at the top or bottom of the page to save your progress, and click Save and Quitwhen you’re done and want to return to the main page for your Template Library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few tips for working with your CSS:
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Copy/paste new code at the bottom of the stylesheet to override default styles. This is a great way to “tweak” your CSS and keep all your custom code in one place. Just keep in mind that as you progress you may eventually want to go back through and merge styles together for ease of maintenence.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Grab a copy of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mozilla.com/&#34;&gt;Mozilla Firefox&lt;/a&gt; if you don’t already have one and use the &lt;a href=&#34;http://getfirebug.com/&#34;&gt;Firebug&lt;/a&gt;extension to examine your staging site in detail so you can pick and choose the right styles to work on. During extensive coding sessions I like to have my CV3 admin open in one tab and my staging site open in another, with the Firebug panel expanded on my staging site. I can pop back and forth and easily review my changes quickly.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Keep your CSS here or in other stylesheets (next section) and out of your HTML. Using inline styles in your HTML will cause lots of problems down the road when you open up your CSS file to make changes and not all of them work anymore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UPLOADING ADDITIONAL CSS FILES&lt;/h3&gt;
Most sites like the simplicity and convenience of having one stylesheet – it keeps everything together in one place. But sometimes you need to include more than one, or you may be working with a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CSS_framework&#34;&gt;stylesheet framework&lt;/a&gt; so you need multiple files. Here’s how you do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First you upload the CSS. In the CV3 left navigation click on File Library under the Design section and then click the Upload File link at the top of the page. Click the Browse button to find the CSS file on your harddrive and then click Upload.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, you’ll need to link to your new stylesheet. Return to your Template Library and expand the Site Design Templates group, which should be the third group in the library. Scroll through the list and find the template called “Meta Tag Information (_meta.tpl)” and click on the name or the edit button to the right of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dig through this file to find this line:
&lt;blockquote&gt;&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”{#stylesheet#}”&amp;gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Add a link to the spreadsheet you just uploaded right above this line:
&lt;blockquote&gt;&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”/downloads/blueprint_screen.css”&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”{#stylesheet#}”&amp;gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Make sure you change the name of the css file to the name of the file you uploaded. You can do this with multiple stylesheets, and you may wind up with something like this:
&lt;blockquote&gt;&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”/downloads/blueprint_screen.css”&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”/downloads/blueprint_fancy-type_screen.css”&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”{#stylesheet#}”&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{* IE online styles *}
&amp;lt;!–[if IE]&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”/downloads/blueprint_ie.css”&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;![endif]–&amp;gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Now don’t take all this as a suggestion to use stylesheet frameworks. Most likely there are better ways to implement your design. But it does illustrate how to include multiple stylesheets and browser-specific stylesheets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So during that process you probably saw a coule of things that scared you. First you saw tons of templates with strange names. Then you opened up a template and saw tons of strange code that didn’t look quite like HTML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relax. It’s not so bad. And when your boss is asking you for more whitespace around the new home page promo, you’re going to be glad you have this kind of access to your templates :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let’s overcome the first fear.
&lt;h3&gt;DECONSTRUCTING CV3 TEMPLATES&lt;/h3&gt;
The pages on your CV3 store are built by assembling all of these templates together. Depending on the page you’re on, it may use one, two, twelve or twenty of these templates to assemble the page the user sees. This is going to get technical, so stay with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default template set does this because we’ve factored out the code that is used over and over again into component files that can be included where ever they are needed. Some people refer to this technique as DRY – Don’t Repeat Yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good example is the _meta.tpl template we looked at earlier. As you can guess from the name and the fact that you include stylesheets in it, this file creates the part of the page between the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; tags, most people call it the header information or the meta information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This stuff is included on every page of your site. So we seperated the code into this small, convenient template. When you want to change the way your meta information works, you change it here and it updates on every page of your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to change the way the shop-by-price search looks? It’s in the left column of your default storefront. Just edit “shopbyprice_menu.tpl”. This file only has 15 lines, because all it does is control the display of one small piece of your page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’re familiar with CV3 Templates, you’ll find yourself searching for a specific template and making a quick change easily, without worrying about accidentally affecting other areas of your site, or forgetting to update something in all the places it appears.
&lt;h3&gt;TEMPLATES INSIDE TEMPLATES&lt;/h3&gt;
Since templates can include other templates, and those can include even more templates, it can be frustrating to find the exact template you want to change. So let’s make a change to the home page to illustrate how you can easily find the template you need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you want to make a change to the Shop By Price area on the left of the home page, but you have no idea what that template is called or what group it’s in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the main page of your template library click Expand All at the top of the page. This will open up all the template groups and show every single template file on your site. Use the Find command in your browser to search for the text “home” or “index”… you’ll quickly find the index.tpl file under the Catalog Display group. Open it up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can probably read the source code and tell what files it includes, but there’s an easier way. At the top of the page there’s a link called “Edit pages this template includes”. Click this link and you’ll see all the “sub-templates” that this template uses. You can click on each one, but at first glance we can probably assume that the stuff in the left navigation is in “_top.tpl”, since in web design left navigation is usually created before the main area of the page, and by process of elimination (two of those templates are promos and the last is the bottom of the page).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So click on “_top.tpl” and the page reloads with that template. Again we could look at the source code, but let’s stick with our template navigation at the top of the page. Now we have two links, “Edit pages calling this template” and “Edit pages this template includes”. This will take some getting used to, but these links are sort of like “up” and “down” links, moving you through the template heiarchy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Edit pages calling this template” will show you “parent” templates, and in this case there are a lot, but the “index.tpl” file we just came from is included in the list, so we can move back “up” to that template if we want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Edit pages this template includes” takes us further “down” the chain, helping us drill down to a specific point on a page. In our case, this is what we want to do, so click this link to expand this section. We see three files and an obvious choice for our next jump – “left_nav.tpl”. We know from viewing our staging site that that’s exactly where we want to make our change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So clicking on “left_nav.tpl” takes us to another short snippet of code that displays the left navigation. If we want to reorder the way things appear in the left nav, we’d do it here. But we want to actually change something more specific, so let’s again click on “Edit pages this template includes” and we see what we want: shopbyprice_menu.tpl. Go ahead and click on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change the text “SHOP BY PRICE” to “Price Shopping” and click Save. Refresh your staging site (it is open in another tab by now, right? If not click Staging in the top bar to the right of the CV3 logo). You should see your change immediately. If not, check to make sure your browser is not caching web pages locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All looks good, so click Save and Quit. Whew! A familiar site, the main page of a template library!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Navigating up and down the template hierarchy in this manner is a great way to explore the CV3 template system and discover how things work. As you get more and more familiar with things you’ll start moving to your file directly. And when you’re a master, you’ll create your own template groups, move the files into the groups you want and establish your own system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So before we go, we need to tackle that other fear… the strange code inside those templates that doesn’t quite look like PHP or HTML.
&lt;h3&gt;LOOPS, VARIABLES AND THE REST OF THE SMART(Y) STUFF&lt;/h3&gt;
We’ve edited CSS and HTML, but what if we want to change something more dynamic. What if we want to adjust the way a product title is displayed, or the way a category page loops through all the products it contains? In these cases, we can’t just edit the HTML because CV3 is pulling stuff out of your database and displaying it dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do this sort of thing you need to work with a language called Smarty. Smarty is an open-source templating language based on PHP, and it has it’s own &lt;a href=&#34;http://smarty.net/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; with tons of information and a great &lt;a href=&#34;http://smarty.net/crashcourse.php&#34;&gt;quick start&lt;/a&gt; of it’s own. But here’s the quick scoop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 templates (.tpl files) are just Smarty templates. When reviewing the Smarty documentation, you don’t have to worry about the PHP stuff, we take care of that for you. All you have to worry about is the .tpl stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few examples of how you use Smarty with CV3:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To display a product name:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{$product.prod_name}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
To capitalize that product name automatically:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{$product.prod_name|capitalize}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
To call another template file in a template:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{include file=”category_sort.tpl}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
The Smarty documentation covers a lot more. My suggestion is to read the crash course and the come back to CV3 and start looking at product and category templates to start to see how Smarty is used. The CV3 templates can get complex, usually because they look for default values for things if there are no custom values for them, but just scan them and the variables and loops you need will start to jump out at you, and you can ignore the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you start really digging into CV3’s Smarty implementation, you’re going to wonder about what data structures are available to you in each template. You can figure out the basics by reviewing the default templates and how they call a product title, or how a featured product rotation is coded on the store’s home page. But when you’re rolling, it’s better to just see a list of everything you have at your disposal. That’s when you need the following command:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{array_debug}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
This command can be placed anywhere, in any template, and it will show you all the variables and arrays available to you. Try putting it at the top of your home page. It will print a link: “Debug All” and when you click this link a panel will open showing you all your data structures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A better way to use array_debug is to give it a specific array or variable to print. It keeps the output smaller and shows you just what you want to see. Here are some examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assigning a variable and immediately printing it to the screen:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{assign var=”subCats” value=$categories.$cid.sub_cats}
{array_debug var=”subCats”}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Displaying an array:
&lt;blockquote&gt;{array_debug var=$products}
{array_debug var=”products”}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{array_debug var=$categories.$cid.sub_cats}&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Don’t worry if you don’t get this to start with… it’s complicated, magical stuff. But it gives you unprecidented power over the way your site not only looks but how it actually works. Using array_debug isn’t going to break anything, just give it a whirl and you’ll start to learn exactly how you want to use it.
&lt;h3&gt;CONCLUSION&lt;/h3&gt;
With great power come great responsibility. The CV3 template system let’s you change anything (literally anything) on your site, so they can be daunting. Designers who launch multiple stores will get faster over time, and learn all kinds of things that will help produce stores faster. And once you create one store, you can use it as your starting template for your second store. In fact, some CV3 users create a special template set that isn’t used in a live store but instead provides a “base” to start from when creating new stores, a base they like better than our default template set.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/careers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We come together for user group conferences, on-site work sessions, camping trips and the occasional paintball massacre. We also interact daily via video conferences, conference calls and instant messaging. It’s a “do-it-yourself” culture that’s not for everyone, but if you are a self-starter and proficient with web-based communication tools, it could be for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We currently are actively recruiting for the following positions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business Development Representative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customer Support Specialist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online Marketing Specialist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sales Representative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send your application, and why you think you’d be a great addition to our team to: &lt;a href=&#34;jobs@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;jobs@commercev3.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Hosting</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/cloud-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/cloud-hosting/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;certified-secure&#34;&gt;Certified Secure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PCI-DSS Compliant platform with Level 1 VISA Certification&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CV3 platform undergoes rigorous and continuous testing by security firms, and the entire platform is certified annually by third party auditors. So CV3 is not only compliant software, but certified software, and it’s certified at the highest level available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fully-automatic&#34;&gt;Fully Automatic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No maintenance, upgrades, or hardware headaches&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensing software is often just the beginning of your investment, but at CV3 everything is included: software upgrades, bug fixes, firewalls, routers, redundant servers, redundant connections, geographically diverse fail-over, system administrators, pager duty… the list goes on an on. The short version: we take care of everything so you can focus on selling product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;flex-up-down&#34;&gt;Flex Up &amp;amp; Down&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add hosting resources for busy times, thin down off-season&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internet traffic fluctuates, sometimes on a regular cycle and sometimes because of an external event like a Superbowl ad. At CV3 we have multiple layers of automatic service allocation going on at any given time. New servers spin up as load increases in the morning and then spin down in the middle of the night. New clusters appear as Cyber Monday approaches and stick around as long as they are needed during the holiday season. All this activity means your store always has plenty of bandwidth  for shoppers but you are paying for it when you don’t need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;edge-speed-with-cdn&#34;&gt;Edge Speed with CDN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Built-in content delivery network for faster page delivery&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speed is a priority at CV3, and milliseconds count. Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are built directly into the way CV3 works, so your data is housed as close to the shopper as possible so your site pops into their browser when they visit. And our CDN usage is easy maintain over time, it works in the background so you don’t accidentally put a bunch of product images in the wrong place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;redundant-data-centers&#34;&gt;Redundant Data Centers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stores are deployed to virtual data centers for true cloud redundancy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 offers multiple layers of redundancy. Clustered server instances mean your shoppers never see a slow down, even if traffic gets high or a couple of instances decide to crash. And if an entire data center goes down (we’ve seen it happen many times), your stores are replicated across multiple data centers in different geographic regions so you don’t have to worry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-tier-add-ons&#34;&gt;Top Tier Add-ons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Globally distributed DNS, mail servers, blog hosting &amp;amp; more&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A successful storefront needs a whole network of supporting services, and your platform is only as strong as its weakest link. No one will get to your super fancy redundant servers if your DNS provider goes down. At CV3 we partner with top-tier global firms like Amazon, NuStar, Rackspace and Sendgrid to make sure all your supporting services are just as stable as your web store.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/our-company/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;schedule-a-demo&#34;&gt;Schedule a Demo&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to evaluate CV3 is to take it for a test drive. Contact our sales team at 888-544-2211 or &lt;a href=&#34;sales@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;sales@commercev3.com&lt;/a&gt; to schedule a great time for a demo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-support&#34;&gt;Get Support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re alway here when you need help. Contact our support team at 888-544-2211 or &lt;a href=&#34;sales@commercev3.com&#34;&gt;support@commercev3.com&lt;/a&gt;. Include all the details you can so we can expedite our response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mailing-address&#34;&gt;Mailing Address&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;13045 MOUNTAIN TRAIL
CLERMONT, FL 34715
PHONE: (888) 544-2211
FAX: (866) 562-9492
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/features/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;platform-specs-certifications&#34;&gt;Platform Specs &amp;amp; Certifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fast &amp;amp; flexible cloud-based application&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multi-server, multi-datacenter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dedicated SQL-based cloud storage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;edge CDN for binary assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;global, multi-homed DNS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;on-demand resource scaling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PCI-DSS Level 1 VISA Certification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;full backup rotation &amp;amp; code escrow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;customization-branding&#34;&gt;Customization &amp;amp; Branding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% editable site, including checkout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;raw HTML &amp;amp; CSS &amp;amp; javascript access&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;open source theming engine (Smarty)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML5 &amp;amp; CSS3 enabled by default&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive mobile design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTML &amp;amp; JS framework friendly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legacy browser support via Modernizr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PHP-style code support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;re-usable “building blocks” of code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;staging area for reviewing changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;internal file and image libraries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A/B testing, including Google W.O.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-shopping&#34;&gt;Web Shopping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flexible product search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;search filtering and results ordering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;optional support for SLI Advance Search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nested category browsing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multiple-product images &amp;amp; videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support for image zoom &amp;amp; effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product ratings &amp;amp; reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;optional inventory control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;related products &amp;amp; required products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;parent / child products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product attributes &amp;amp; sets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;volume pricing discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;minimum quantity limits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;customizable products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product assemblies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;mobile-shopping&#34;&gt;Mobile Shopping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive, mobile-first design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;use HTML5, JQuery Mobile and more…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;target multiple mobile platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;shopper toggle between mobile &amp;amp; web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;configurable default for tablets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ajax-based content loading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;full shopping &amp;amp; expedited checkout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;theme updates retain customizations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-shopping&#34;&gt;Social Shopping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook like buttons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product ratings &amp;amp; reviews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;share buttons, e-mail products to friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embedded shopping in Facebook&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;international-features&#34;&gt;International Features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;language-specific theme support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;set language-specific currency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;international shipping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;international payments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;traffic-building-seo&#34;&gt;Traffic-building / SEO&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;customizable, friendly URLs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;canonical URLs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;customizable meta-data per page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;additional user-defined page data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;redirect mapping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;landing pages with add-to-cart&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Site Map support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;membership&#34;&gt;Membership&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;view previous orders / track orders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;quick-reorder / address book&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;view gift certificate balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;marketing-promotions&#34;&gt;Marketing &amp;amp; Promotions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;catalog request &amp;amp; e-mail sign-up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;referrer tracking &amp;amp; media code support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;add-to-cart dynamic landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;segmented customer groups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;behavioral group triggers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;individual &amp;amp; group promo codes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;single-use promo codes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fixed &amp;amp; percentage promos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;category-based promos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;free shipping promos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;volume-based discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;customer-based discounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“stackable” promos &amp;amp; exclusions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;link-based auto-adds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;checkout&#34;&gt;Checkout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;express &amp;amp; full checkouts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;member &amp;amp; non-member ordering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fully branded checkout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom SSL certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pre-checkout recipient mapping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pre-checkout shipping estimator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon / Google / Paypal checkout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;shipping-tax&#34;&gt;Shipping &amp;amp; Tax&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multiple-ship to support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;shipping tables, groups and shippers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product-specific shipping rates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;perishable shipping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fed-Ex / UPS / USPO integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom shipping API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom tax tables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multi-state tax exemptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product-specific tax exemptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avalara / Exactor / CCH tax integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom tax API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;payments&#34;&gt;Payments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;purchase orders &amp;amp; invoice me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gift certificate &amp;amp; card on file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;electronic check / eCheck.net&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;private label credit cards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authorize.net / Chase Paymentech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paypal’s Payflow Pro &amp;amp; Payflow Link&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paypal’s Web Site Payments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TransFirst ePay / USA ePay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sterling / Litle &amp;amp; Co / Virtual Merchant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mercury Payment Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;order-management&#34;&gt;Order Management&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;order batch processing &amp;amp; PDF copies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mail Order Manager integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quickbooks Enterprise integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StoneEdge Order Manager integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural Order integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NewHaven CMS &amp;amp; Wizard integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OrderMotion integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CoLinear Response integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reporting-analytics&#34;&gt;Reporting &amp;amp; Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Analytics integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;full traffic &amp;amp; revenue reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;virtual square-inch analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;competitor tracking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;percentile key metrics ratings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;api-external-access&#34;&gt;API / External Access&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;secure SOAP-based XML API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;two-way information exchange&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;update product details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;update inventory counts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;batch process orders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sync customer data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;push shipping status/tracking number&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Services</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/growth-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/growth-services/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;online-marketing-cv3-experts&#34;&gt;Online Marketing &amp;amp; CV3 Experts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-proven-active-responsive-leader-in-multi-channel-retail&#34;&gt;A Proven, Active &amp;amp; Responsive Leader in Multi-channel Retail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team includes SEO experts, paid search campaign managers, email campaign designers, site usability experts, web programmers and systems administrators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have launched hundreds of storefronts and helped our customers generate more than a billion dollars in revenue online. And unlike much of our competition, we’re not just consultants. We suggest tools and then roll up our sleeves and install them. We craft elegant designs, then cut them up and build out HTML pages. We hone email copy and then test it through various email ﬁlters for high-deliverability. We help our clients rank well in the search engines and get positive ROI from online advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, we don’t just create a map and send you off on your own. We work right alongside you to help you succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;part-consultant-part-developer-part-marketer&#34;&gt;Part consultant, part developer, part marketer.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 works in concert with clients. We effectively provide the type of services, solutions and skills required to achieve success in today’s highly competitive online marketplace. We build relationships on a foundation of trust and with an eye towards long-term success. Our team is comprised of online marketing experts, professional designers, software developers, client specialists, team developers and network specialists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more&#34;&gt;Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;marketing&#34;&gt;Marketing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 wants to be more than just your eCommerce platform, we want to be your growth partner. Let us utilize our extensive knowledge of the digital universe and make us a part of your planning, research, development, marketing, social interaction and analysis &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;partner-program&#34;&gt;Partner Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 Exclusive Partner Program With our innovative Partner Program you’ll receive proactive guidance with your online marketing and focused attention to help guide your website, all centered on growing your e-commerce sales.  We will provide the str&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing Products</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/docs/importing-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/docs/importing-products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;INTRODUCTION&lt;/h3&gt;
The CommerceV3 Product Import allows users to, in its most basic usage, import an entire inventory at store creation time and, in its most advanced usage, maintain inventory via a single spreadsheet that can be used to create and update products in the online store.
&lt;h3&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;/h3&gt;
Uploaded import files are pipe- or tab-delimited files that contain product, sub-product and attribute data.  The file can include any of the possible fields in any order you would like.  The only limitations are that the SKU must be present for product lines, the SKU and ParentSKU must be present for sub-product lines and ParentSKU, IsAttribute and Attribute1 – Attribute* (* = the number of attributes you have for that product) must be present in attribute lines.  These fields are used as the keys when updating and linking your products. Other than that you can include as many of the fields as you would like to update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first line of the import file is the header line.  In the header line you will define which fields you will be using.  Remember, they can be in any order you would like.  The remaining lines will contain product data with the information corresponding to the fields you defined in the header line.  The only limitation here is that sub-products and attributes need to fall below its parent product. See below for examples.
&lt;h3&gt;AVAILABLE FIELDS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;pre&gt;
SKU                               | required in Product and Sub-Product lines
ProdName
ProdDescription
Brand
Manufacturer
IsRetail                          | “TRUE”,”FALSE”  Note: IsRetail defaults to TRUE if RetailPrice is set
RetailPrice*                      | Products can have multiple price categories.  * represents the value linking the
RetailPriceCat*                   | price, price category and special price and should be incremental numbers.
IsWholesale                       | “TRUE”,”FALSE” Note: IsWholesale defaults to TRUE if WholesalePrice is set
WholesalePrice
WholesaleQty
ProdStatus                        | “In Stock”,”Out of Stock”,”Backordered”,”Discontinued”
ProdInventory
OutOfStockPoint
ProdOnOrder
AltID
VendorID                          | the ID of the drop-shipper for the product
DescriptionHeader
ProductURLName                    | must be unique
SpecialPrice*                     | * represents the value linking price, price category and special price
IsSpecialOngoing                  | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
SpecialStart                      | format: mm-dd-yyyy hh:mm
SpecialEnd                        | format: mm-dd-yyyy hh:mm
SpecialText
BackorderedDate                   | format: mm-dd-yyyy
IgnoreBackorder                   | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
MinimumQuantity                   | &lt;strong&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/strong&gt;
MaximumQuantity                   | &lt;strong&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/strong&gt;
QuantityInSet                     | &lt;strong&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/strong&gt;
NumIterationsDisplayed            | &lt;strong&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/strong&gt;
DisplayWeight
ActualWeight
Unit                              | “none”,”each”,”tsps”,”tbs”,”cps”,”oz”,”pts”,”qts”,”ml”,”l”,”lbs”,”dz”,”pr”,”gal”,”sheet”
ImageSetThumb*                    | Products can have multiple image sets.  * represents the value linking the thumbnail, large,
ImageSetLarge*                    | and popup, type, and title for each image set. NOTE: This does NOT upload images.  These are
ImageSetPopup*                    | links only. The images must already exist on an external server or in your store.
ImageSetType*                     | “product” or “color_swatch”
ImageSetTitle*                    |
ImageSetEditType                  | “overwrite”,”append”  choose to overwrite current image sets or append to the end of the list.  The default is “overwrite”.
IsInactive                        | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsOutOfSeason                     | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsTaxExempt                       | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
HasTextField                      | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsHidden                          | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsFeatured                        | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsNew                             | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsGoogleCheckoutExempt            | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsContentOnly                     | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsInventoryExempt                 | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
IsSubscription                    | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
SubscriptionPrice
HasElectronicDelivery             | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
ElectronicDeliveryLink*           | products can have multiple electronic delivery documents
ElectronicDeliveryDaysAvailable*  | * represents the value linking the Link, DaysAvailable and Description
ElectronicDeliveryDescription*    |
ElectronicDeliveryEditType    &lt;strong&gt;COMING SOON&lt;/strong&gt;    | “append”,”overwrite”  choose to overwrite current electronic delivery links or append new ones.  The default is “append”.
IsKit                             | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
KitProductSKUs                    | comma separated list of SKUs
ShipPreference                    | “tables”,”fixed”,”both
FixedShipping
ShipsInOwnBox                     | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
PackageLength
PackageWidth
PackageHeight
FreightClass
IsGiftCertificate                 | “TRUE”,”FALSE
GiftCertificateDaysAvailable
GiftCertificateValue
Rating
Keywords
MetaKeywords
MetaTitle
MetaDescription
CategoryIDs                       | comma separated list of category IDs
Custom1
Custom2
Custom3
Custom4
Custom5
Custom6
Custom7
Custom8
Custom9
Custom10
Custom11
Custom12
Template
DependencySKUs                    | comma separated list of SKUs
DependencyType                    | “AND”,”OR”
AdditionalProdSKUs                | comma separated list of SKUs
RelatedProdSKUs                   | comma separated list of SKUs
GiftWrap                          | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
GiftWrapName                      |
GiftWrapSKU                       |
GiftWrapAmount                    |
CategoryFilter*                   | products can have multiple category filters and values
CategoryFilterValue*              | * represents the value linking the filter with the value
ParentSKU                         | required for sub-product and attribute lines
SubProductAttributes              | comma separated list of attributes
IsAttribute                       | “TRUE”,”FALSE”  – required for attribute lines
AttributeTitle1                   | attribute titles are set in the parent product line
AttributeTitle2
AttributeTitle3
AttributeTitle4
AttributeSKU
Attribute1                        |
Attribute2                        | Required to update attribute
Attribute3                        | information
Attribute4                        |
Attribute1Code                    |
Attribute2Code                    |
Attribute3Code                    |
Attribute4Code                    |
AttributePrice*                   | Attributes can have multiple price categories.  * represents the value linking the
AttributePriceCat*                | price, price category and special price and should be incremental numbers.
AttributeSpecialPrice*            | * represents the value linking price, price category and special price
IsAttributeSpecialOngoing         | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
AttributeSpecialStart             | format: mm-dd-yyyy hh:mm
AttributeSpecialEnd               | format: mm-dd-yyyy hh:mm
AttributeBackorderedDate          | Format: mm-dd-yyyy
AttributeIgnoreBackorder          | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
AttributeInventory
AttributeOutOfStockPoint
AttributeOnOrder
IsAttributeInactive               | “TRUE”,”FALSE”        Note:this field will be ignored if AttributeStatus exists
AttributeStatus                   | “active”, “inactive”, “deleted”, “discontinued”
IsAttributeGiftCertificate        | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
AttributeGiftCertificateDaysAvailable
AttributeGiftCertificateValue
IsAttributeSubscription           | “TRUE”,”FALSE”
AttributeSubscriptionPrice&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXAMPLE IMPORT&lt;/h3&gt;
This is an example import file that includes all available fields as well as all product types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://commercev3.smackdabcentral.com/files/2009/07/example_import.tab&#34;&gt;Download Example Import&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a breakdown:
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;pre&gt;
Line 1: Header Line
Line 2: Regular Product (no sub-products or attributes)
Line 3: Product Containing Sub-Products
Line 4: Sub-Product 1 for Product in Line 3
Line 5: Sub-Product 2 for Product in Line 3
Line 6: Sub-Product 3 for Product in Line 3
Line 7: Products Containing Attributes
Line 8: Attribute 1 for Product in Line 7
Line 9: Attribute 2 for Product in Line 7
Line 10: Attribute 3 for Product in Line 7
Line 11: Product with Electronic Delivery
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXAMPLE INVENTORY ONLY IMPORT&lt;/h3&gt;
This is an example import file that only updates inventory counts for the products in above example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://commercev3.smackdabcentral.com/files/2009/07/example_inventory_only_import.tab&#34;&gt;Download Inventory Only Example Import&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrations</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/integrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/tour/integrations/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;order-inventory&#34;&gt;Order &amp;amp; Inventory&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colinear’s Response&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DEACOM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freestyle Solutions’ Multichannel Order Manager – M.O.M.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MACH Software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monsoon Stone Edge’s Order Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural Solution’s Natural Order&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neesvig’s Fulfillment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NewHaven Software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OrderMotion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QuickBooks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SAP Business One&lt;em&gt;COMING SOON&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SYSPRO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TCRDS Incorporated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel &amp;amp; custom integrations via the CV3 Open API&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;advanced-search&#34;&gt;Advanced Search&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compliment built-in search with advanced 3rd-party tools&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SearchSpring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SLI Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tax-solutions&#34;&gt;Tax Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avalara&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CCH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exactor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom integration via any URL-based post/response script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;shipping&#34;&gt;Shipping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Federal Express (FedEx)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United States Postal Service (USPS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ABF Freight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;custom integration via any URL-based post/response script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;payment-gateways&#34;&gt;Payment Gateways&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choose your payment processor—we connect to them all&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authorize.net / Authorize.net CIM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chase PaymenTech – Tampa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cybersource&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elavon VirtualMerchant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eMerchant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Litle &amp;amp; Co&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merchant e-Solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mercury Payment Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paypal Payflow Pro, Payflow Link, Website Payments Pro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sterling Payment Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TransFirst ePay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USAePay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verifone Payware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verisign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;email-marketing&#34;&gt;Email Marketing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking email marketing to the next level&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bronto&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/marketing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Your continued success is important to both of us, so who better to implement your digital marketing than a company that is vested in your success?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-we-offer&#34;&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initial evaluation of your online marketing goals resulting in a custom crafted plan of initial and long term recommendations. Goal: Increase sales by bringing additional qualiﬁed trafﬁc to your site, and additionally driving a higher conversion rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Paid Search (PPC)&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll help you hone and optimize your AdWords advertising to reach your ROI and budget goals. CV3 deliverables may include: key term research, installation of tracking codes, development of multiple campaigns and ad groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Remarketing Banner Ads Set up and Installation&lt;/em&gt; – this is an extension of your PPC campaign and shows visitors to your site (who then leave without purchasing) ads when they visit other sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Shopping Submission&lt;/em&gt; – We strongly recommend Google Shopping ads. These ads generate sales and provide good exposure through the prominence given to the shopping results on Google search results pages. CV3 will create a product feed, add Google Analytics tracking codes, and submit it to Google Shopping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Email campaign suggestions and expert advice&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll make recommendations on how to enhance the design and content of your emails to increase your sales. And then we’ll help you execute those ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Email Template Design/Code&lt;/em&gt; – It takes just a split second for an email recipient to choose whether to engage with an incoming email. CV3 has done extensive research in effective email design and successful deliverability. Our designers use the latest email code standards to ensure the highest rates of deliverability, as well as proven design features to elicit high click through rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Checkout Optimization&lt;/em&gt; – CV3 marketing experts will review and optimize the shopping cart and checkout process with an eye towards removing obstacles to conversion, deleting unneeded form ﬁelds or checkout steps, and adding images or messages that emphasize security and guarantee. We may also adjust button hierarchy and design on each page, create a custom shopping cart header, and remove unnecessary menu links which keep customers from completing the checkout process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Search Engine Optimization&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll work to ensure that your website is optimized.  You can also rely on us to provide ongoing guidance on good SEO practices as part of your monthly services. Search engine optimization will include: keyword research, development of title tags, meta descriptions for your home page and category pages, setup of a Google Webmaster Tools account, and submission of your new sitemap to Google and Bing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Analytics Installation and enhancement&lt;/em&gt; – Google Analytics is our analytics platform of choice, and we conﬁgure it for your website. We’ll double check the installed analytics code on the site, and setup checkout goals and funnels and analyze the results as they come in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project Management&lt;/em&gt; – We will oversee and manage these projects and work with your team to coordinate email dates, PPC scope, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Media guidance&lt;/em&gt; – our team can review your current social media efforts and provide suggestions. Often we can give you recommendations and then provide training to your own staff so they can do the posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mobile&lt;/em&gt; – We can also help you evaluate your mobile CSS and make recommendations to increase conversion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>