<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on CommerceV3</title>
    <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on CommerceV3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.commercev3.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Services</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/growth-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/growth-services/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;online-marketing-cv3-experts&#34;&gt;Online Marketing &amp;amp; CV3 Experts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-proven-active-responsive-leader-in-multi-channel-retail&#34;&gt;A Proven, Active &amp;amp; Responsive Leader in Multi-channel Retail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team includes SEO experts, paid search campaign managers, email campaign designers, site usability experts, web programmers and systems administrators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have launched hundreds of storefronts and helped our customers generate more than a billion dollars in revenue online. And unlike much of our competition, we’re not just consultants. We suggest tools and then roll up our sleeves and install them. We craft elegant designs, then cut them up and build out HTML pages. We hone email copy and then test it through various email ﬁlters for high-deliverability. We help our clients rank well in the search engines and get positive ROI from online advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, we don’t just create a map and send you off on your own. We work right alongside you to help you succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;part-consultant-part-developer-part-marketer&#34;&gt;Part consultant, part developer, part marketer.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 works in concert with clients. We effectively provide the type of services, solutions and skills required to achieve success in today’s highly competitive online marketplace. We build relationships on a foundation of trust and with an eye towards long-term success. Our team is comprised of online marketing experts, professional designers, software developers, client specialists, team developers and network specialists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more&#34;&gt;Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;marketing&#34;&gt;Marketing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 wants to be more than just your eCommerce platform, we want to be your growth partner. Let us utilize our extensive knowledge of the digital universe and make us a part of your planning, research, development, marketing, social interaction and analysis &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;partner-program&#34;&gt;Partner Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 Exclusive Partner Program With our innovative Partner Program you’ll receive proactive guidance with your online marketing and focused attention to help guide your website, all centered on growing your e-commerce sales.  We will provide the str&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/marketing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Your continued success is important to both of us, so who better to implement your digital marketing than a company that is vested in your success?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-we-offer&#34;&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initial evaluation of your online marketing goals resulting in a custom crafted plan of initial and long term recommendations. Goal: Increase sales by bringing additional qualiﬁed trafﬁc to your site, and additionally driving a higher conversion rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Paid Search (PPC)&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll help you hone and optimize your AdWords advertising to reach your ROI and budget goals. CV3 deliverables may include: key term research, installation of tracking codes, development of multiple campaigns and ad groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Remarketing Banner Ads Set up and Installation&lt;/em&gt; – this is an extension of your PPC campaign and shows visitors to your site (who then leave without purchasing) ads when they visit other sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Shopping Submission&lt;/em&gt; – We strongly recommend Google Shopping ads. These ads generate sales and provide good exposure through the prominence given to the shopping results on Google search results pages. CV3 will create a product feed, add Google Analytics tracking codes, and submit it to Google Shopping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Email campaign suggestions and expert advice&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll make recommendations on how to enhance the design and content of your emails to increase your sales. And then we’ll help you execute those ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Email Template Design/Code&lt;/em&gt; – It takes just a split second for an email recipient to choose whether to engage with an incoming email. CV3 has done extensive research in effective email design and successful deliverability. Our designers use the latest email code standards to ensure the highest rates of deliverability, as well as proven design features to elicit high click through rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Checkout Optimization&lt;/em&gt; – CV3 marketing experts will review and optimize the shopping cart and checkout process with an eye towards removing obstacles to conversion, deleting unneeded form ﬁelds or checkout steps, and adding images or messages that emphasize security and guarantee. We may also adjust button hierarchy and design on each page, create a custom shopping cart header, and remove unnecessary menu links which keep customers from completing the checkout process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Search Engine Optimization&lt;/em&gt; – We’ll work to ensure that your website is optimized.  You can also rely on us to provide ongoing guidance on good SEO practices as part of your monthly services. Search engine optimization will include: keyword research, development of title tags, meta descriptions for your home page and category pages, setup of a Google Webmaster Tools account, and submission of your new sitemap to Google and Bing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Analytics Installation and enhancement&lt;/em&gt; – Google Analytics is our analytics platform of choice, and we conﬁgure it for your website. We’ll double check the installed analytics code on the site, and setup checkout goals and funnels and analyze the results as they come in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project Management&lt;/em&gt; – We will oversee and manage these projects and work with your team to coordinate email dates, PPC scope, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Media guidance&lt;/em&gt; – our team can review your current social media efforts and provide suggestions. Often we can give you recommendations and then provide training to your own staff so they can do the posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mobile&lt;/em&gt; – We can also help you evaluate your mobile CSS and make recommendations to increase conversion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partner Program</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/partner-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/partner-program/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cv3-exclusive-partner-program&#34;&gt;CV3 Exclusive Partner Program&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will provide the strategy and execution of all initiatives around SEO, PPC, email, website optimization to drive revenue growth within your store. The Partner Program is paid for by way of a small revenue share of the growth that we help you to realize, therefore, we have a vested interest in your success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CommerceV3 is inviting you to join our exclusive Partner Program Community. We have isolated our key assets and personnel to support members of this top tier community with remarkable support for every part of your website. Here’s how your business would benefit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;dedicated-phone-and-email-support-with-one-contact-point&#34;&gt;Dedicated phone and email support with ONE contact point&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be assigned a dedicated account executive to manage the team and the tools engaged in growing your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;direct-access-to-staff-in-all-key-areas-including&#34;&gt;Direct access to staff in all key areas including:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-Going Site Development and Enhancements – be the first to implement the newest tools to engage your customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Application Training – Email, interactive, and Phone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;monthly-marketing-calls-review&#34;&gt;Monthly Marketing Calls/Review&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monthly calls to review digital marketing and social media analytics and adjust marketing tactics accordingly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;25-discount-on-all-production-and-development-work&#34;&gt;25% discount on all production and development work&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because we are now aligned to your success, we will share in the cost of development and production by providing a significant discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;annual-goals-planning&#34;&gt;Annual Goals Planning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Site Review and marketing planning to achieve your annual sales goals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Services</title>
      <link>http://www.commercev3.com/services/technical-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.commercev3.com/services/technical-services/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;commercial-support&#34;&gt;Commercial Support&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some merchants use CV3 on their own, but the vast majority work with our team on a monthly or quarterly basis to refine their online channel and achieve growth goals. We provide one-on-one or team-based training via web or on-site sessions so that your staff stays up to date on the latest e-commerce trends, features and growth tools available in CV3. When there’s an issue on your storefront, our support team is there to troubleshoot and assist in the resolution. We respond quickly to emails and phone calls, and when we’re not at work, our emergency response team is still available 24 hours a day should there be a crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;re-platforming&#34;&gt;Re-platforming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change is never easy, so we provide a dedicated project manager to make sure your move to CV3 is seamless. Your CV3 project manager can also pull in our designers, developers and marketers throughout the launch process as needed to accomplish specific tasks. In particular our SEO team works meticulously to maintain your existing web traffic throughout the transition while priming it for growth once the transition is complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;integrations&#34;&gt;Integrations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CV3 was built from the ground up for multi-channel retailers, so our platform is ready to plug into a wide variety of third party software out of the box. From analytics packages to order management software to e-mail service providers, there’s a lot of integrations that are simple to activate and configure from within the CV3 admin area. For more complex integrations, custom ERP packages or home grown systems, we have a comprehensive API that is easily consumed via simple web requests. We also have a team of seasoned integration programmers and a wealth of open source connector modules that can work with your team to complete any integrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;front-end-development&#34;&gt;Front-end Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide a wide variety of front-end web development services. We design and redesign high-growth storefronts. We develop and optimize storefronts for short load times and a variety of screen sizes from screen to tablet to mobile phone. We work hourly when fast-turnarounds are needed on small changes, or we can provide ongoing management plans for larger projects. We provide all these services on any e-commerce platform, not just CV3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;back-end-development&#34;&gt;Back-end Development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need something CV3 can’t do out of the box? Our development team specializes in e-commerce add-ons, integrations and related apps of all sizes. If it involves products, customers, orders, fulfillment, shipping, analytics or any combination of the above, we’ve been there and done that many times. We’ve developed complex connectors, touch-based kiosks, product configurators, wholesale ordering systems and more. Contact us for more details on your specific project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>